<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>jeremyschroeder</title><description>jeremyschroeder</description><link>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/blog</link><item><title>Southside Pride says, &quot;Go to your precinct caucus April 4&quot;</title><description><![CDATA[On Tuesday, April 4, you'll have a chance to influence the direction of our city in a very meaningful way. I hope you will join us at caucus and consider becoming a delegate to the Ward 11 convention on April 29. It's a small time commitment with a big payoff. Reach out to the campaign if you have questions, and we'll be happy to talk through the process with you!This week, the Southside Pride highlighted Jeremy's experience in their coverage of the city council races. You can read the full<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_e61addfa574841d3b08e65319defad29%7Emv2_d_3433_2833_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fill/w_626%2Ch_517/fc1800_e61addfa574841d3b08e65319defad29%7Emv2_d_3433_2833_s_4_2.jpg"/>]]></description><link>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2017/01/11/Go-to-your-precinct-caucus-April-4</link><guid>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2017/01/11/Go-to-your-precinct-caucus-April-4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 18:18:06 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>On Tuesday, April 4, you'll have a chance to influence the direction of our city in a very meaningful way. I hope you will join us at caucus and consider becoming a delegate to the Ward 11 convention on April 29. It's a small time commitment with a big payoff.Reach out to the campaign if you have questions, and we'll be happy to talk through the process with you!</div><div>This week, the Southside Pride highlighted Jeremy's experience in their coverage of the city council races.<a href="http://southsidepride.com/go-to-your-precinct-caucus-april-4-2/">You can read the full story here!</a></div><div>&quot;Jeremy Schroeder is currently policy director for the Minnesota Housing Partnership, an organization that advocates for affordable housing. He supports raising the minimum wage to $15 an hour, and he told Southside Pride: 'I previously served as executive director of the Illinois Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty. I am the only candidate in Ward 11 who has worked with community members, victims of crime and law enforcement to reform the criminal justice system. I am eager to use that experience to improve relations between our city’s residents and police officers. I will leave it up to Ward 11 voters to decide which candidate is best equipped to help our city heal from the tragic deaths of Mr. Clark and Mr. Franklin, and prevent similar tragedies from happening in the future.'&quot;</div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_e61addfa574841d3b08e65319defad29~mv2_d_3433_2833_s_4_2.jpg"/></div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Meet Team Schroeder | Bryana</title><description><![CDATA[I grew up in the Ward 11 neighborhood and moved back (a mile from my childhood home) when I returned to Minnesota after 11 years. I love this neighborhood for its abundance of beautiful parks, closeness to Lake Nokomis, central location, safety, and friendliness. Jeremy and his family were the neighborhood welcome wagon (as I affectionately call them) for me when I moved in 2.5 years ago and have helped me feel incredibly welcomed and part of the community. As a Black biracial woman and<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_cffe7d96aa184dc99b694a3465952562%7Emv2.jpg"/>]]></description><link>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2017/01/10/Meet-Team-Schroeder-Bryana</link><guid>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2017/01/10/Meet-Team-Schroeder-Bryana</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>I grew up in the Ward 11 neighborhood and moved back (a mile from my childhood home) when I returned to Minnesota after 11 years. I love this neighborhood for its abundance of beautiful parks, closeness to Lake Nokomis, central location, safety, and friendliness. Jeremy and his family were the neighborhood welcome wagon (as I affectionately call them) for me when I moved in 2.5 years ago and have helped me feel incredibly welcomed and part of the community. As a Black biracial woman and psychology professor, whose career is in social justice and multicultural education, this feeling of belonging is critical. Not only does Jeremy have an all accepting interpersonal style, but his work experience is incredible. He's fought for justice in numerous ways, including raising minimum wage and abolishing the death penalty. In these uncertain, hateful, and frightening political times, we need more people who understand how to fight and win for equity and the importance of diversity, inclusion, and justice. I know that Jeremy has my back and have complete confidence in him as my city council representative.</div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_cffe7d96aa184dc99b694a3465952562~mv2.jpg"/></div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Meet Team Schroeder | Christine and Ron</title><description><![CDATA[When you live across the street from someone, you get to see how he is every day, in all kinds of situations. I'm here to bear witness to the daily awesomeness of Jeremy Schroeder, who is running for Minneapolis City Council in 2017. We've lived in Diamond Lake for 19 years, and we think Jeremy offers just the sort of leadership our neighborhood needs. If you live in Ward 11—or even if you don't—I invite you to support this smart, hardworking, cool-headed, kind, and funny human being in his<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_c7a6e1331471406d8bce60730c7279f0%7Emv2_d_2048_1715_s_2.png"/>]]></description><link>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2017/01/03/Meet-Team-Schroeder-Christine-and-Ron</link><guid>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2017/01/03/Meet-Team-Schroeder-Christine-and-Ron</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 21:10:42 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>When you live across the street from someone, you get to see how he is every day, in all kinds of situations. I'm here to bear witness to the daily awesomeness of Jeremy Schroeder, who is running for Minneapolis City Council in 2017. We've lived in Diamond Lake for 19 years, and we think Jeremy offers just the sort of leadership our neighborhood needs. If you live in Ward 11—or even if you don't—I invite you to support this smart, hardworking, cool-headed, kind, and funny human being in his campaign. It'll wash the nasty taste of 2016 politics right out of your mouth.</div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_c7a6e1331471406d8bce60730c7279f0~mv2_d_2048_1715_s_2.png"/></div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>&quot;In Minneapolis City Council races, so far there's left, and further left&quot;</title><description><![CDATA[In a field of left and further left challengers, I'm proud to represent both a progressive agenda and an approach grounded in a career of collaboration with views different than my own. My mention in this Star Tribune article is small, which I consider to be good. I believe in the importance of healthy dialogue with opposing viewpoints.Our city is stronger when we listen to everyone at the table and also actively seek out those opinions not represented at the table. As the article points out,<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_6a4c5c88499b4e59876b13451cd561d5%7Emv2.jpg/v1/fill/w_529%2Ch_387/fc1800_6a4c5c88499b4e59876b13451cd561d5%7Emv2.jpg"/>]]></description><dc:creator>Jeremy Schroeder</dc:creator><link>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2017/01/03/In-Minneapolis-City-Council-races-so-far-theres-left-and-further-left</link><guid>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2017/01/03/In-Minneapolis-City-Council-races-so-far-theres-left-and-further-left</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>In a field of left and further left challengers, I'm proud to represent both a progressive agenda and an approach grounded in a career of collaboration with views different than my own.<a href="http://www.startribune.com/in-minneapolis-city-council-races-so-far-there-s-left-and-farther-left/409231255/">My mention in this Star Tribune article</a>is small, which I consider to be good. I believe in the importance of healthy dialogue with opposing viewpoints.</div><div>Our city is stronger when we listen to everyone at the table and also actively seek out those opinions not represented at the table. As the article points out, caucus night will be vital to our campaign.If you’d like to know more about the process and/or get involved in our caucus campaign, sign up here!</div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_6a4c5c88499b4e59876b13451cd561d5~mv2.jpg"/></div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Happy Holidays from Team Schroeder!</title><description><![CDATA[We have had an exciting first couple of months on the campaign. As we move rapidly towards the end of 2016, we can reflect on all the progress we’ve made. We’ve sent out letters of introduction to our neighbors outlining my vision for Ward 11. We’ve reached over 400 followers on Facebook and printed our first piece of literature. Dedicated supporters around the neighborhood have hosted wonderful house parties!Next year will bring more of the same, plus some new initiatives, new literature, new<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_5dba014c3f9d48a191b4bc80f06cf4e1%7Emv2.png/v1/fill/w_125%2Ch_53/fc1800_5dba014c3f9d48a191b4bc80f06cf4e1%7Emv2.png"/>]]></description><dc:creator>Jeremy Schroeder</dc:creator><link>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2016/12/14/Happy-Holidays-from-Team-Schroeder</link><guid>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2016/12/14/Happy-Holidays-from-Team-Schroeder</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 17:48:56 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>We have had an exciting first couple of months on the campaign. As we move rapidly towards the end of 2016, we can reflect on all the progress we’ve made.</div><div>We’ve sent out letters of introduction to our neighbors outlining my vision for Ward 11. We’ve reached over 400 followers on Facebook and printed our first piece of literature. Dedicated supporters around the neighborhood have hosted wonderful house parties!</div><div>Next year will bring more of the same, plus some new initiatives, new literature, new events and new outreach!</div><div>We couldn’t do it without you!If you’d like to help us start the year right, please consider donating to the campaign today.Whether you can spare $25 or $250, anything helps! We’ll put that money toward outreach and we always promise a clean, transparent, issues-based campaign!</div><div>Happy Holidays and Happy New Year to all! I hope you get a chance to get out and enjoy this great Minnesota snow!</div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_5dba014c3f9d48a191b4bc80f06cf4e1~mv2.png"/><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/93b6b4_3e7a33c280434ca48f0aa166bc387149~mv2.jpg"/><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/93b6b4_15b34ca04f9949c891861a1941aff321~mv2.jpg"/></div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Southwest Journal Features Schroeder Campaign</title><description><![CDATA[The Jeremy for Minneapolis campaign is thrilled to share the recent Southwest Journal feature story.  Journalist Dylan Thomas interviewed Jeremy and provides additional information about his platform and vision for Ward 11.  “I’m not running to be an elected official; I’m running to get things done,” Jeremy says .  The Southwest Journal article continues  by explaining "Schroeder said he would be a more 'proactive, engaged' leader at City Hall, pledging to be a transparent decision-maker who is<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_dcdd5e462470444e88b0cc0898d3d275%7Emv2.jpg"/>]]></description><link>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2016/12/08/Southwest-Journal-Features-Schroeder-Campaign</link><guid>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2016/12/08/Southwest-Journal-Features-Schroeder-Campaign</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 15:30:36 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fc1800_dcdd5e462470444e88b0cc0898d3d275~mv2.jpg"/><div>The Jeremy for Minneapolis campaign is thrilled to share the recent Southwest Journal feature story.  Journalist Dylan Thomas interviewed Jeremy and provides additional information about his platform and vision for Ward 11.  “I’m not running to be an elected official; I’m running to get things done,” Jeremy says .  The Southwest Journal article continues  by explaining &quot;Schroeder said he would be a more 'proactive, engaged' leader at City Hall, pledging to be a transparent decision-maker who is responsive to the residents of Ward 11.&quot;</div><div><a href="http://www.southwestjournal.com/news/2016/12/nonprofit-executive-to-challenge-quincy-in-ward-11/">Read the full article here.</a></div></div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Meet Team Schroeder | Casie and Matt</title><description><![CDATA[As a mom of two young kids, I spend a lot of time walking up and down my block. And it's such a great block: there are people of all ages, different religious faiths, different races and ethnic backgrounds, super progressives and super conservatives, renters and homeowners. And when we have the chance to gather on someone's patio, we have such a great time together. I love living in Minneapolis because it is a place where neighbors can really connect and care about each other, no matter our<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/f90c7e_8baaa7cdd01348f783b5efcc43499e92%7Emv2_d_4608_3072_s_4_2.jpg"/>]]></description><link>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2016/12/08/Meet-Team-Schroeder-Casie-and-Matt</link><guid>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2016/12/08/Meet-Team-Schroeder-Casie-and-Matt</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>As a mom of two young kids, I spend a lot of time walking up and down my block. And it's such a great block: there are people of all ages, different religious faiths, different races and ethnic backgrounds, super progressives and super conservatives, renters and homeowners. And when we have the chance to gather on someone's patio, we have such a great time together. I love living in Minneapolis because it is a place where neighbors can really connect and care about each other, no matter our differences. I am voting for Jeremy Schroeder in 2017 to represent Ward 11 because he loves Minneapolis, too, and wants to make sure that it is a place where all residents have the opportunity to thrive.</div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/f90c7e_8baaa7cdd01348f783b5efcc43499e92~mv2_d_4608_3072_s_4_2.jpg"/></div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Meet Team Schroeder | Geoff and Emily</title><description><![CDATA[As parents of an amazing little girl, we couldn’t be happier that we chose to live in Minneapolis. When we found out Elena was deaf, we not only had access to amazing doctors, non-profits, hospitals and schools; we had options – amazing options on how she could and would thrive. We want Elena to grow up valuing differences – including her own – and being among others who do the same. I support Jeremy because he has empathy for families and their unique situations, values the importance of<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/f90c7e_dbc9301ee8e54e68934b8dfd5181b485%7Emv2_d_3072_2481_s_4_2.jpg"/>]]></description><link>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2016/12/06/Meet-Team-Schroeder-Geoff-and-Emily</link><guid>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2016/12/06/Meet-Team-Schroeder-Geoff-and-Emily</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>As parents of an amazing little girl, we couldn’t be happier that we chose to live in Minneapolis. When we found out Elena was deaf, we not only had access to amazing doctors, non-profits, hospitals and schools; we had options – amazing options on how she could and would thrive. We want Elena to grow up valuing differences – including her own – and being among others who do the same. I support Jeremy because he has empathy for families and their unique situations, values the importance of neighbors being engaged and taking part in their community, and has experience to navigate government to get some pretty great things accomplished.</div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/f90c7e_dbc9301ee8e54e68934b8dfd5181b485~mv2_d_3072_2481_s_4_2.jpg"/></div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Join Team Schroeder</title><description><![CDATA[Joining the Jeremy Schroeder for City Council campaign is a practical, tangible way you can make a difference in your community. Not only does city government impact your life on a day-to-day basis, but also  the lives of your family, friends, and neighbors. You can decide how involved you want to be, and we'll do all the training. Join us in making Minneapolis a more vibrant place for everyone who lives here.     Sign up here to join the team!]]></description><link>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2016/11/01/Join-Team-Schroeder</link><guid>http://www.jeremyschroeder.org/single-post/2016/11/01/Join-Team-Schroeder</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>Joining the Jeremy Schroeder for City Council campaign is a practical, tangible way you can make a difference in your community. Not only does city government impact your life on a day-to-day basis, but also  the lives of your family, friends, and neighbors. You can decide how involved you want to be, and we'll do all the training. Join us in making Minneapolis a more vibrant place for everyone who lives here.Sign up here to join the team!</div></div>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>